It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going on the stage.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
Know what you're making, my dream time to.
Don't you feel it, I
really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
The greater no day I know you.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wild, girl.
I'm no afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you.
It's my life, it's your life.
But it won't you move on?
It's what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your call.
Let's keep on going, rolling.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your wife that I
want, but you're weary once.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you're gonna kick your fast.
Let's keep on going, I'm not dead.
You make my day every day.
Lord Pika isn't moving anymore.
Is it okay for him to
lose his head like that?
Who did that to him?
Let's strike while we can.
Dopplomingo shall die by
my hand. No mine. No mine.
Those stubborn bastards don't
know when to give up, do they?
Fire!
Don't let them get to the palace!
Why don't you bring out someone
worth fighting next time?
We gave it our best.
But we can't stop the
fighters from the Coliseum.
Those little rats are really
fired up, aren't they?
They actually think they have a
chance against the young master.
They're throwing their lives away.
Indeed so.
Once Fujitora arrives at
the palace with his marines,
they'll be ground up with a capital G.
I had a feeling that
was Straw Hat's group.
They did stop Lord Pika.
We have four different enemies
approaching the palace right now.
First, there's the
competitors from the Coliseum.
Second, there's Kidos.
Next, there's a second in
command of the Straw Hats.
Lastly, there's Straw Hat
Luffy and that traitor Law.
This must be the place!
Pervert convert!
Smile Factory! Wow! Wow-ow!
I hate me some gates and I'm
downright disrespectful to doors!
Get a load of my radical beast!
For the record, that crappy beam of yours
wouldn't even put a dent in the factory.
I came here for one reason.
To settle our score.
Haven't I fought you enough?
A man's battle never ends.
You got that boy?
Wow, that was an awesome
bird, senor! Shut up!
I'm begging you, Kiros.
Walk out from behind there
and surrender yourself.
If you don't do that, then
we'll come and get you!
We aren't doing this for money.
We don't turn you in,
then everyone's gonna die!
There's no other choice!
We just want to bring an end to
this nightmare as soon as possible.
I can't blame you for
wanting to end this quickly.
And I certainly don't disagree.
But if that's the case, then
I need to move even faster!
Don't let anyone get away!
I won't lose.
But there is something
that I must do first.
What's the deal?
Does this mean Mr.
Luffy's not here?
Of course not.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
Luffy never stays anywhere for
more than five minutes at a time.
Ah!
Now that's freedom! Whoo!
The king of the pirates
knows how to roll, huh?
All right, that's everyone.
It looks like those pirates
aren't giving up yet.
Just a little further, men!
We're almost to the top!
Since we're done with the
net, perhaps I'll put it away.
Goodbye. Oopsie.
She's so classy.
What's that big monster?
Come take a look.
What is the royal palace
doing way up there?
I got the key.
Viola!
Viola.
Father, did you see?
I have the keys to lost handcuffs.
I was able to find it
thanks to my clairvoyance.
Now to get it to Straw Hat.
Viola, wait.
Why place your faith in them?
They're criminals.
That's fine.
Our kingdom must be broken
down and its lies exposed.
They'll do that.
I trust them to end this false beast.
So I'm betting everything
on the Straw Hats.
The world government has
proven untrustworthy.
They gave a title to Doflamingo,
who ruled this kingdom with cruelty.
Who caused our family so
much pain and suffering.
They're blind to the
meaning of justice and
deaf to the voices of
those they've victimized.
They don't understand our rage.
People in authority have the privilege
of only hearing what they want to hear.
But Straw Hat, he acts on the
goodness inside his heart.
Even though he's a pirate,
he hasn't lost his humanity!
I'll give Doflamingo the biggest
beating of his life for you!
Make sure you guys all
live to see it, okay?
This might change your mind, King Rick!
I want you to look at this man!
The one worth five stars?
That's right!
Usaland, a .k .a.
God Usa.
He risked his life and faced
off with trouble and sugar.
He freed the people who had been enslaved
as toys and brought
everyone's memories back.
He is the hero of our people.
Usaland, go!
And Luffy Land is his
captain, so he's super, too.
Please believe me.
The Usolanders, or rather the Straw Hats,
are the greatest hope
that Dressrosa's got.
Even though they're pirates, I'll trust
them and cheer them on till the very end.
Hey, Viola.
Can I deliver the key to Lucy for you?
I don't know.
I can't just stand here and wait.
Let me go. Rebecca.
Okie dokie, sounds great.
Let's go see Mr. Luffy.
Don't worry, I'll keep you nice and safe.
Just count on me! That's no good.
Or did you forget that you're
on Doflamingo's wanted list?
People will hunt you down. I'll be fine.
We'll lead the way.
On the rooftops!
Cub and I know how to handle this.
Don't worry!
On the rooftops? That's right.
Hey, Inhal, can I leave
the factory in your hands?
No problem.
I already checked in
with the scouting unit.
They said Fraland is fighting
Senor Pink at the gate as we speak.
We'll rush over and
help him any way we can.
We'll take back Princess Mon
Cherie and all our friends, too.
Until next time, then.
All right, people, we've
sat around for long enough.
We'll complete our missions and meet
back here on the King's Plateau.
Are you guys ready? Yeah!
Straw Hat Luffy.
He really does seem to
have a mysterious power.
Pirates are...
Go Flamingo!
This is wrong!
Wrong!
How did those muscle heads
make it this far this fast?
We were supposed to have
thousands of marines down there.
Maybe they're sleeping.
I could understand them
getting past the troops,
but Bastille and Fujitoru
were supposed to be there too.
Are these guys crazy strong
and somehow we didn't know?
Is that all they have to stop us?
The Don Quixote family is weak!
You'll reach their boss in no time!
Yee-haw!
I have a report!
Straw Hat Loopy has arrived
at the base of the...
Oh!
Come, come!
Coming!
Open!
Sorry, sir.
We tried.
But he's too tough.
A Straw Hat.
They are so done for!
The Colosseum group is on its way!
I'm coming.
Those Colosseum guys are moving too!
I can see that, Dellinger.
Seems like there's something
holding up the navy.
What is it?
I don't suppose if I asked
nicely, you'd move out of my way.
I stand with the Straw Hat Pirates and
with those who have risen up to join them.
So if you or any of your friends
want to lay a finger on them,
you're not taking another step.
Not on my watch.
Giving cover to pirates, is that
the Revolutionary Army's job?
It is now, and I think I can
say that as Chief of Staff.
More so, I say that as a brother.
I see.
Though that begs the question of
who your dear sibling might be.
Yeah, we'll see.
I told you so.
I ate the flame flame
fruit, if you didn't know.
Huh?
I don't care what kind of power you got,
the Navy's not gonna lose just
cause of one guy with a stupid pipe!
I'm telling you, don't shoot! Fire!
Why won't you listen to me?
What the hell, man?
Nobody's finger should be that strong.
These are claws.
Fire, man!
He ate a logy of fruit.
He's a monster.
I admit this has become quite the tragedy.
Step aside.
You'd better leave this one to me!
You better hold on, Kitty, because I'm
about to clip those claws of yours.
A cat, huh?
These are the claws of a dragon.
Claws that liberate the innocent
and tear down oppressors like you.
He did that with his fingers?
The thing broke in half.
How dare you?
And by the way, once these
claws clutch a human skull,
they can shatter it to pieces like an egg.
Well, this is quite the quandary.
I brought down a meteor,
but come to think of it,
the birdcage is likely to cut it
into pieces before it gets here.
Yeah?
Uh-oh.
Run away!
Ah, man.
I should have thought through that one.
I made a real mess of things.
I don't even know where
all the pieces went.
I hope I didn't harm any civilians.
Warn us before you drop a
meteor next time. It's scary.
I brought down a meteor. Real sorry.
Too late!
You realize this could get terribly ugly.
I'm still getting used to my new powers.
I'm lucky I was able to ward that off.
Vice Admiral!
Are you all right, sir?
No, no, I said so!
You really have caused quite the mess.
You mentioned your duty as a brother.
Yeah?
I can't help but be
reminded of Firefist Ace.
When he possessed your same power
before he died at Marineford,
he said that Straw Hat Luffy was
his brother, though not by blood.
So are you also his brother?
All it takes to become brothers
is to share some sake. Brothers!
The three of us exchanged a cup of sake.
Even in death, our bond will never break.
I must say that's a rather troublesome
little family you've got there.
One of them is enough!
An upstart with a massive bounty!
A former commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates!
And the Chief of Staff from
the Revolutionary Army!
Mark my words.
No matter where I am, no
matter what I'm doing,
even if I must abandon my duties,
The moment that Luffy needs
my help, I'll be there.
I won't let him down.
Sabo! Sabo!
Never again.
I think I've asked enough questions.
Hardly any point.
Sorry.
Was I boring you?
I like a story better when I
can enjoy it with a cup of sake.
Luffy.
Luffy, I swear!
I'll protect you!
Go, go, go, go!
That's the Colosseum's Grim Reaper, but
why does it have Straw Hat on its back?
As long as we keep him away
from the palace, we're good!
He'll lose the game eventually!
You leave Moosey alone!
Alright, Moosey!
Grim Reaper, coming through!
Get out of the way!
Can't you see?
We're in a hurry!
Cabbage!
Pardon me, but I'll be taking the lead.
Dammit!
I thought I was taking
a shortcut for sure!
We gotta pick up the pace, Moosey, okay?
Crap!
Now everyone's catching up to us!
It's I-Rudan!
Move it!
I don't have time to play with you chumps!
I've got some place to be!
This sucks! We're losing!
Here he comes!
Not again!
Don't blink!
Shoot the ball!
Hey, you bunch of crab bags.
Keep your paws off Straw Hat, or else...
Who's that?
You're breaking my heart, kid.
Come on, I'm from Block C.
The same round as you, remember?
It's Kelly Funk!
You sure?
Your buddy god, Usopp,
really saved my tail today.
Just being friendly!
Anyway, I found a shortcut you can use.
It'll take you straight to the sunflower
field, right in front of the palace.
Seriously?
This is the least I can do.
Alright, let's leave cabbage in the dust!
Hey, Straw Hat.
I still gotta get these handcuffs off.
There's no point in reaching
the palace if I can't fight
at this rate.
Doflamingo will just kill me.
Work out, at least I think so.
What if you're wrong?
We need to go back to that plateau.
Why to find the key?
If we don't win this
fight, them we're all dead.
See that? Shortcut. Told ya.
What are you waiting for? Go ahead.
I'll stay here and keep watch
for you. Thanks. Sounds awesome.
Moosey, let's go.
Best of luck.
Thanks for the tip, my friend.
And thanks for guarding the entrance, too.
Will do you proud.
Oh well, we didn't need them, did we?
Nope, no looking back! Let's go!
To the sunflower field!
We'll be all right.
You just keep going.
That's your snail, isn't it? Get it.
Hello?
This is Luffy, the man who's
gonna be king of the pirates.
Hi, Luffy. It's me.
Robin!
Right now, we're at the plateau.
Same as before. And you?
We're at the bottom of that other plateau,
on the way to some sunflower field.
That's four levels up.
Nice progress.
Good news.
Viola found the key to the cuffs.
Let's meet up.
Oh, awesome! Great. Let's hurry.
Where should we go?
This is Leo, from the Tantana tribe.
Real soon, Miss Rebecca,
the big rooster guy.
And Robiland will be escorted
to your nearest location.
at super high speed.
Luffy, we'll meet at the
sunflower field. That's perfect.
Uh, but how are you guys
gonna catch up with us?
I'll explain later.
You just worry about
getting there. Peleck.
See?
It all worked out.
Yeah, by coincidence.
We're off to the sunflower field, Moosey.
Turn back.
This place is flooded.
It's a dead end. Get out. Hurry.
Don't panic, Moosey.
Someone's coming!
It's you!
Doflamingo!